Merry Christmas, everyone!
I am Sana Murohara.
I am Seina Sato.
I am Taguchi Inari.
Yes, so today
This is Likoira's first karaoke project!
Yay!
Yes, that's right, this time
The name of the event is
If we can all have fun singing together...
Oh, I made a mistake.
Yay! I made a mistake!
The name of the song
If everyone can have fun singing together
Ricoira's Christmas Karaoke Project, where she wants to get a score of 97 points!
Yes!
Can you do it?
Kiruji is sleeping, right?
You can do it again, right?
That's right! It's Christmas!
Let's have fun!
Anyway, our main goal is to have a fun karaoke party with the three of us.
But, just in case, it's a loose plan to arrange Kiruji's music!
Please enjoy it!
Arrangement of Kiruji
Let's play that song.
Let's go.
It's strange how I feel now, you're falling from the sky
To the color of a special miracle
This melody I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop
I can't reach the sadness
Then I'll tell you already, let's work together
Until our feelings overlap
I'm sorry, but it's too late.
I can't even stop in the middle of the sweets.
I'll give you the courage to jump in and I'll protect you.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for your hard work.
Till the love grows on top of the love.
I don't know what to say.
I'm so sorry
It's going to pass
In a slight fever
No one else can do it
You're giving me the courage to tackle it.
Soon we'll start
Jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan
Jan, jan, jan, jan, jan, jan
Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan, Jan.
Here you go.
You're so good on the high notes, aren't you?
Very good!
I'm sorry.
That was fun.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Boring!
It's always fun.
Yes, it is.
Let's do it.
Oh, shit.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Are you okay?
Oh!
Oh! I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
There he goes.
Oh, my God!
Wow! It's going!
Oh, my God, you're doing great.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're doing great, guys.
Let's get dressed up today.
Let's get dressed up.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's good.
It's good.
Oh, it's good!
This year, the body temperature árias e
Work degree
this?
In the sky with a rainbow
Huh?
The sound of crying ears
For example, in the hall.
Someone's friendship
I don't care if I'm clouding someone's friendship
I'm the only bad guy here.
I'm always the bad guy
With anyone.
I used to remember you.
And now you're telling me that we can't have that.
I'm gonna have to get rid of it here.
It's so far away.
Hazure!
Beautiful!
I wonder how much I can get rid of the fear
I wonder how much I can get rid of
I'll let out a reassurance, I'll shout out a resounding yes, a yes that I've heard so many times before
I still can't forget the hand in my pocket that frightened me
-end-
good night
I'll miss you, but I'm going
Even though I'm not the same as I longed to be someday
Only one, only you
I wanted to be strong enough to protect you
I wanted that more than anything.
And now this.
Go far, far ahead
I know it's too young to love
Even if the world is pointing at us from behind
I'm not lost, just keep going, keep going, keep going
Into a universe that's just the two of us
I trembled in my pocket
With my hand now
Your hand
Take me out of here
This is Kanbar
Emotion is the fundamental law of unity
History is your
I love you
Come on, even when the wind seems to blow us away
I clumsily hold your hand
This hand, well...
Never let go
To the end of the rainbow
Yes!
That's good.
It's fun.
Super fun.
It's so good!
Wow!
Yuuchan!
Ah!
Go ahead.
Don't let it happen for a second.
It's hard.
Don't go at all.
Thank you for your time.
What do you want me to sing?
Uh...
No, I don't know.
Oh, no!
Goodbye!
Let's do it.
Let's do it!
What? Wow, this brings back memories!
No one's out.
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa! What are you kids doing?
There's a lot of them.
Have a nice day.
Your love story, it's predictable.
I'm playing myself right now.
I've been there for you, but in the end I'm just a spectator.
That emotionless soliloquy, it's always the same.
You get used to it. It's not so bad.
It's a life of romance, if you ask me.
I've learned to love it.
I wish I could have chosen a different design, a different relationship
I wish I'd had a choice of worlds to meet
I wish I'd had a different personality I wish I'd had a different set of values
I wish I could tell you how much I love you
Assuming love is the way to run away from your hands
I'm not the one you're meant for
It's hard but I can't stay but I can't leave
I can't stay, but I can't leave
Just touching it hurts, but it's sweet, no, no, no, goodbye
What are you to me then? I don't know the answer, and I don't want to know.
If there's one thing I know for sure, you're beautiful.
Goodbye, the man in your arms is not me It hurts, but I can't deny it, but it's hard to leave
It hurts just to touch you. No, but it's sweet. No, no, goodbye.
What are you to me then? I don't know the answer. I don't want to know.
But if there's one thing I know for sure, you're beautiful.
But romance and turtles aren't so bad, are they?
Yes, they are.
You're very beautiful.
It's good.
Smile.
That's not a song you sing with a smile on your face.
Come on, let's get going.
The hand of departure.
Failure happens
I don't care if I want to go, I can't.
Thank you.
òn
I'll get started.
Private beds...
I can do this video now.
Too funny.
What was that song again?
Can I look it up?
How are you doing?
Have you found someone special?
Will your dreams come true someday?
At the end of the road.
Do you remember that evening of swaying wheat?
I kept looking for a sky that would continue to the horizon.
While struggling to paint tomorrow, I'm now in my dream
Softly, softly, gently embracing the brightness of things that have no form
Don't go on.
Are you smiling? Is the rain as innocent as that day?
I bet you laughed through the cold night and the rainy morning, didn't you?
If your hometown is the place you want to go back to, it's right here.
It's always waiting for you just the same.
Oh, wow, even on cold nights and rainy mornings, if there's a place to go home, it's right here.
I'll always be the same, waiting for you
Oh, great, even on cold nights and rainy mornings
Don't stop drawing, in this dream
The warmth of your loved one... forever and ever...
Don't forget to keep going
People are lost and she's lazy
Oh, a little this way
A little this way
I'm looking at it
I want to stare at the brightness of a time that will never be again
It hurts!
I'm in a dream while smiling
Softly, softly, gently embracing the shine of things that have no form
I go forward.
I'm going forward.
You're good!
She's beautiful!
Beautiful.
Can I see more?
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
She's doing one song.
Yeah, like that.
Me, too.
I'm not doing one song right.
I'm fine.
You've got it just about right, Kiara.
Thank you. Thank you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
You're gonna want to see this.
It's just, uh, you know, it's true.
If I hadn't arranged it like that.
If we hadn't wasted so much time arranging it.
Oh, shit.
That's so hard.
Oh, man.
I want to hear Ciara's voice.
Oh, my God, I'm so nervous.
I get nervous easily.
I get nervous easily, so why don't we just turn it up a little bit? I'm just gonna...
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, no.
You're all over, Kana Nishino.
What are you doing?
Special Colors
Sometimes I forget when I get close.
Four of them, right?
Be selfish.
Be kind to me as you are
Wrap me in your arms
I just want to stare at it.
Oh, this view.
Will be the same for a hundred years
I want it to stay the same forever
As the night wind turns a little chilly
The jacket you gently draped over me
Wrapped in your fragrance
I want to keep having gentle dreams
When I'm too happy, I get scared
I checked the space
Like a star that seems to exist in this sky
Don't let it disappear
If time would stop like this
I'd like to gaze at it together
This view, reflected a hundred years in the future
I want it to stay the same forever
Our hearts must change a little
Thank you for watching
May it never change
Forever
Don't change forever
Okay!
Good!
It's good!
It's done!
They're waiting for you, sir.
We'll be waiting.
Good, good, good.
AI is really normal
Thank you for your hard work.
I understand.
So don't say anything.
Tell the truth.
Take a breath
Don't hold back.
♪ Don't hold back anymore ♪ ♪ Just for me ♪
♪ And show me your heart
With eyes that look like they're about to cry
More than I like you
And the clumsiness of living defenselessly
Broken things must be protected.
They'll break you.
I'll always protect you.
I'll hold you.
With a broken heart
With a heart that's afraid and broken
You could have waited for me
I found you, your nuance
If you're a broken thing
If it's a thing, the ship will be destroyed.
I'll always protect you, I'll always hold you
fragile, fragile, fragile feelings, don't break them
I'll always protect you, I'll hold you
Fragile
I'll hold you forever, don't break my fragile, fleeting thoughts
I'll give you a blow!
I feel a blow!
Why?
I'm going to feel it someday.
Thank you for watching.
I'll be there.
Oh!
Wow.
Woah!
Aaahhh!
I'm going home!
I'm leaving, I'm leaving, I'm leaving!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no! Good, good, good!
But you got your goal!
We did it!
Let's sing a fun song for the last three of us.
Let's sing something.
Heroines sing Heroines.
I always sing Heroines with a color kick.
Why?
Is Ricoh Love in there? Please tell me your name.
Kyun Stamp, Fun Kyun Stamp.
Oh, yeah!
I won't let you in there if you're the last one standing.
This is what life is all about on EVE.
Oh, yeah!
Ooo-gee.
Are they singing what they just sang?
The balance of eves.
You're gonna switch?
L.O.V.E.T.A.T.E.
Mynower.
Keep on making noise.
Man's wife Official
Tires kept away from neighboring countries
L.O.V.E.T.A.T.E.
I'll drop it.
Inside me Come to lose
Jab jab jab jab jab
Jab jab jab jab jab jab
You're a little more
Harmon, your face
Come on, come here
Tension, Echora.
Oh-oh time
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta
Mahoolah.
Amael Borer
Catter gutter
All the way.
L.O.V.E.T.A.T.E.
Prayer
Do you like Ee-chan?
Not everything.
Actier.
Paradaroo.
Actia
BPM up with coffee
L.O.V.E.T.A.T.E.
Lucky
Jab Jab
Eco-Babu is the best!
I'm gonna hit it!
No one can see
No one
Happy engineer
Lucky Engineer
Indram is here to see you
Wave to me, wave to me, wave to me some more
Let the spide's voice echo
Because you're all I've got
Yes, thank you
Rising feelings Smiles People our attitude You and the lid idol
En on bri in sur ka man su mitomi
I'll light up everyone!
No, no, no!
Hachiri tsukkidemo raito
En on, in, sir, in, sir, on yellow
I'm gonna light up everyone's hearts
No, no, no!
En on in sir ka man su en on in sir on yellow
Your hair's on a swivel, your cheeks on the floor
Peachy, peachy, staccato
When you fall in love, I shake my head
I'll sing for you
S.O.V. sister shame
I wish I could be that voice you like
On a day when there's make believe bread and flowers I like the way things are going somewhere
S.O.V. sister shame
I don't need to change tonight
With a kiss appeal shameful hard work
I wanted to love you just the way you like it
I've been waiting for you all day
Seino
Love, love, love, love
Love, love, love
Love. Love.
Thank you How is everyone?
Searching, crossing over Thank you, I love you
Even in the distance, I feel your love
With your finger, to the future now
Let's go!
Giggle, giggle, and make it sound, you know, cute
I don't want to be the first
Right hand elbery collaboration
Woo-ya!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Lazy, lazy, lazy, lazy
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
This is the part where I didn't hear anything.
What?
Hana-chan's introduction.
I didn't hear anything.
Oh?
Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no, no, no.
This one's not so easy.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Okay, so...
I'm done!
I achieved my goal!
I saw it for the first time! I was surprised too!
That's amazing! You knew it was going to happen!
I knew you would go for it!
Bye!
That was some really loose karaoke!
It was my favorite karaoke competition because I'll be there soon!
Bye bye! Thank you!!!